Guide to the Tobacco Collection, 1828-1987 and undated, bulk 1870-1955 RL.01300
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Listing By Format
  - Poster, Watson & McGill, Black Swan (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Watson & McGill, Britannica (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Watson & McGill, Crusader (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Watson & McGill, The Enchanter, 2 items (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Watson & McGill, Grand National (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Watson & McGill, Harlequin (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Watson & McGill, The International (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Watson & McGill, MacRae Fine Tobacco (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Watson & McGill, Triumph (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, T.C. Williams Co., Dash (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, T.C. Williams Co., Diadem of Old Virginia (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, T.C. Williams Co., Golden Eagle, 2 items (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, T.C. Williams Co., Juno (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, T.C. Williams Co., Lucy Hinton (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, T.C. Williams Co., Nosegay (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, T.C. Williams Co., Victory (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, T.C. Williams Co., Welcome Nugget, 2 items (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Unknown, Good Times /Honey Dew (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Unknown, Stolen Kisses (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Unknown, Tiger Brand (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Unknown, _____ Trademark (Oversize-box 1)
  - Posters, Wm. Cameron & Bro., Courage, 2 items (Oversize-box 1)
  - Slides (35 mm.), W. Duke, Sons & Co., Tobacco Advertising & W. Duke & Sons., 2 items (Box 6)
  - Souvenir Albums of Card Inserts, Allen and Ginter
    - Birds of the Tropics (Box 1, Acc. 10-31-1990)
    - City Flags (Box 1, Acc. 10-31-1990)
    - Fish from American Waters (Box 1, Acc. 10-31-1990)
    - Quadrupeds (Box 1, Acc. 10-31-1990)
    - World's Beauties (Box 1, Acc. 10-31-1990)
    - George Washington (Box 1, Acc. 10-31-1990)
    - Our Navy (Box 1, Acc. 10-31-1990)
  - Tobacco Pouch with Rolling Papers, W.T. Blackwell & Co., Bull Durham (Box 4)
  - Tobacco Stamps, U.S. Internal Revenue, First Series, Unknown, Ten Pounds Stamps: Nos. A 120563, 120565, and 120568, 3 items (Box 3)
  - Tobacco Stamps, U.S. Internal Revenue, First Series, Unknown, Forty Pounds Stamps: Nos. A 294794 and 327216, 2 items (Box 3)
    Re-issue authorized by Act of June 6 1872, & cancelled with new steel die required by that Act, for use by manufacturers of plug and fine-cut chewing tobacco, & issued Sept. 30, 1873, by collector of 6th District, N.C., County Line, Davie County.
  - Trade Bill & Letter, R.F. Morris & Son M'f'g. Co., Ladies Choice & North State Mills Scotch Snuff & Smoking Tobaccos, 1897 July 1 (Box 1)
  - Trade Cards, Baydex Cigarettes, "African Types," 1930s, 24 cards (Box 1)
  - Trade Card, Boehm, Bendheim & Co., Tobacco Commission Merchants (Box 1)
  - Trade Card, Hall & Daniel, Little Kate Chewing Tobacco (Box 1)
  - Trade Card, The Geo. W. Helme Company, Helme's Railroad Snuff (Box 1)
  - Trade Card, A.G. Howard & Co., Rabbit Foot Cigars, 2 items (Box 1)
  - Trade Card, Lea & Noell, I am at Banner Warehouse Ed. M. Pace. (Box 1)
  - Trade Card, Ledbetter & Co., Tom P. Ledbetter with Ledbetter & Co. (Box 1)
  - Trade Card, Liggett & Myers, Clipper Navy Plug (Box 1)
  - Trade Card, P.H. Mayo & Brother, Inc., Eglantine & Ivy (Box 1)
  - Trade Card, Parriah & Blackwell, Want… (Box 1)
  - Trade Card, A.J. Simonds, Allen's Jewel Plug (Box 2)
  - Trade Card, W.L. Venable & Co., Carolina Belle Scotch Snuff (Box 2)
  - Trade Card, The Watson Warehouse, Watson Warehouse (Box 2)
  - Trade Card, M.V.B. Weighill, Rose Maccoboy, Rappee and Scotch, Railroad Snuff (Box 2)
  - Trade Card, Goodwin & Co., Old Judge (Box 1)
  - Trade Cards (Insert), American Tobacco Company, Herbert Tareyton Cigarettes, 27 items (Box 5)
  - Trade Cards (Metamorphic), W.T. Blackwell & Co., Blackwell's Genuine, 1876 (Box 6)
    Durham, Rutherford B. Hayes and Samuel Tilden.
  - Trade Cards (Shape cards), W.T. Blackwell & Co., Blackwell's Genuine Cigarettes and Long Cut (Box 6)
  - Trade Cards: foreign, Unknown, Regie Française (Sultanes) (Box 3)
  - Trade Cards: foreign, Unknown, Regie Française (Gitanes) (Box 3)
  - Trade Cards, W. Duke, Sons & Co., Circus Entertainers, 2 items (Box 6)
  - Trade Cards, W. Duke, Sons & Co., Actresses (Mounted) (Box 6)
  - Plate, Lone Jack Cigarette Co., Lone Jack Cigarettes (Box 1)
  - Wrappers, F.W. Felgner & Sons, Miners' Extra Smoking Tobacco, 2 items (Box 1)
  - Wrappers, A. Ralph & Co., Ralph's Carolina Snuff, 2 items (Box 2)
  - Wrappers, G.W. Gail & Ax of Baltimore, Navy, 5 items (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Wrappers, American Tobacco Company, Liberty Long Cut Tobacco, 7 items (Box 5)
  - Wrappers, American Tobacco Company, Mayos Cut Plug Wrappers, 2 items (Box 5)
  - Wrappers, American Tobacco Company, "111" Cigarettes, 4 items (Box 5)
    "111" Cigarettes made between 1903 and 1950.
  - Wrappers, American Tobacco Company, U.S. Marine Cut Plug, 12 items (Box 5)
  - Wrappers, American Tobacco Company, Victory Wrappers, 27 items (Box 5)
  - Wrappers, W.T. Blackwell & Co., Durham, 2 items (Box 6)
  - Wrappers, G.W. Gail & Ax of Baltimore, Navy Smoking Tobacco (Box 6)